BRANISLAV VUCETIC

Software Developer

Contact

Novi Sad+381 63 546 933

vucetic985@gmail.com

vuceticBranislav

VuceticBranislav-Portfolio
VuceticBranislav-BRAINS-ACADEMY-2020

Languages

English – B1 Norwegian – A1

Interests

Programming Board Games Video Games

Personal Skills

Problem solving Curiosity Desire to learn Highly motivated

Summary

Over year and a half of experience as a junior software developer in .NET and Azure. Involved in banking backend development. Collaborated on projects with international teams. Successfully transitioning from a 12-year mechanical engineering career. Additionally, I have a long lasting passion for Delphi programming and exploring various languages and technologies. Committed to ongoing learning and development.

Education

♦ Jan 2021 - October 2021:

<u>BRAINS Online 2020</u>, National IT requalification program 5-module course thought by VOICT leading to Java Junior Web Developer level competences. Completed with teacher's commendation

♦ Sep 2006 – Jul 2010:

Master of Science degree in Mechanical Engineering, Production Engineering study programme, Faculty of Technical Sciences, University of Novi Sad.

♦ Sep 2003 – Sep 2006:

Mechanical Engineer, Technical College "Viša Tehnička Škola", Zrenjanin.

Projects

♦ BRAINS ACADEMY - 2020:

Back-end server for simple school register. Involving MySQL database and Spring Boot with authentication and user login functionality. Frontend for book organizer. Written using React with Formik and MUI libraries. Frontend support book management and user logging.

♦ Banking Backend – 2023:

Developement of scalable cloud-native core banking backend using .NET and Microsoft Azure technologies. Using Azure portal and RuleCube beside other tecnologies.

♦ Mainframe modernization – 2023:

Modernize old banking VISA transaction processor written in COBOL to .NET. Some tecnologies used on project are Dapper, Nuke, Bamboo, Kibana, Bitbucket...

Working Experience

May 2011 - Jan 2022:

♦ Mechanical Engineer - Hitard Engineering, Office Novi Sad.

Preparing and review of mechanical drawings and calculations of pressure vessels.

Jan 2022 - Jun 2023:

♦ Junior Software Developer – Levi9, Office Novi Sad.

Backend developement using .NET and Microsoft Azure. Modernize old COBOL mainframe code to .NET.

Jun 2023 – Present:

♦ Senior Mechanical Engineer – Hitard Engineering, Office Novi Sad.

Preparing and review of mechanical design drawings and calculations. Author of various inhouse calculations according to general mechanics.

Basic Level Skills

- ♦ C#, Delphi, Java
- ♦ React
- ♦ Entity Framework ,Hibernate
- ♦ SQI
- ♦ JavaScript, HTML5, CSS
- ♦ Git / GitHub, Bitbucket
- ♦ Postman
- ♦ Azure, AWS
- ♦ Bamboo
- ♦ Kibana